jseblod-cck.com 2017-06-28

# Privacy Policy

Octopoos, Editor of SEBLOD, is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the seblod.com Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the SEBLOD website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

## Collection of your Personal Information

Octopoos collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Octopoos also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Octopoos. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Octopoos for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Octopoos Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Octopoos public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Octopoos does not read any of your private online communications.

Octopoos encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Octopoos so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Octopoos is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Octopoos and Octopoos family of Web sites. Use of your Personal Information.

Octopoos collects and uses your personal information to operate the Octopoos Web sites and deliver the services you have requested. Octopoos also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Octopoos and its affiliates. Octopoos may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Octopoos does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Octopoos may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Octopoos may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Octopoos, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Octopoos does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Octopoos keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Octopoos, in order to determine what Octopoos services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Octopoos to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Octopoos Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Octopoos or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Octopoos; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Octopoos, or the public.

CNIL's declaration number: 1820995 v 0 ([www.cnil.fr](http://www.cnil.fr/ "CNIL"))

## Changes to this Statement

Octopoos will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Octopoos encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Octopoos is protecting your information.

## Contact Information

Octopoos welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Octopoos has not adhered to this Statement, please contact us: [contact form](https://www.seblod.com/contact/). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
